<resources>
    <string name="app_name">CycleMe</string>

    <string name="logout_message_confirmation">Are you sure want to logout?</string>
    <string name="yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="no">No</string>
    <string name="enter_a_valid_email">Enter a valid email</string>
    <string name="password_must_be_filled">Password must be filled</string>
    <string name="minimum_8_characters">Minimum 8 characters</string>
    <string name="emailexample">abc@mail.com</string>
    <string name="email">Email</string>
    <string name="password">Password</string>
    <string name="password_example">********</string>
    <string name="login">Login</string>
    <string name="don_t_have_an_account">Don\'t have an account?</string>
    <string name="register">Register</string>

    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="full_name">Full Name</string>
    <string name="home">Home</string>
    <string name="feed">Feed</string>
    <string name="recycle">Recycle</string>
    <string name="market">Market</string>
    <string name="account">Account</string>
    <string name="rewards">Rewards</string>
    <string name="hi">Hi,</string>
    <string name="let_s_reduce_waste_on_earth_by_recycling_nthanks_for_your_contribution">Let\'s reduce waste on earth by recycling.\nThanks for your contribution</string>
    <string name="share_cycleme_to_your_friends">Share CycleMe to your friends</string>
    <string name="get_started">Get Started</string>
    <string name="get_insights_about_waste_recycling">Get insights about waste recycling</string>
    <string name="popular_recycling_material">Popular Recycling Material</string>
    <string name="browse_materials_that_are_commonly_recycled">Browse materials that are commonly recycled</string>
    <string name="upload_photo_title">Use AI to make idea recommendations from your photo</string>
    <string name="upload_photo">Upload Photo</string>
    <string name="take_picture">Take Picture</string>
    <string name="result">Result</string>
    <string name="result_description">based on your photos, AI analysis recommends the following ideas</string>
    <string name="category">Category: </string>
    <string name="accuracy">Accuracy: </string>
    <string name="switch_camera">Switch Camera</string>
    <string name="failed_to_take_picture">Failed to take picture</string>
    <string name="failed_to_open_camera">Failed to open camera</string>
    <string name="submit">Submit</string>
    <string name="choose_the_materials_you_want_to_recycle_into_high_value_items">Choose the materials you want to recycle into high-value items</string>
    <string name="desc_detail_recycle">Here\'s some recommendation ideas</string>
    <string name="upload_story">Upload Story</string>
    <string name="picture_uploaded_by_user">Picture uploaded by user</string>
    <string name="c_points">C-Points</string>
    <string name="_0">0</string>
    <string name="get_to_know_c_points">Get to know C-Points</string>
    <string name="what_is_c_points">What is C-Points?</string>
    <string name="what_is_c_points_description">C-Points is a virtual point accumulated automatically each time you have done scanning and upload your work. You’ll obtain 10 C-Points for every work uploaded on feed.</string>
    <string name="what_can_c_points_do">What can C-Points do?</string>
    <string name="what_can_c_points_do_description">You can redeem your C-points for rewards once it has reached some certain value on the reedem page. Remember, rewards can only be exchanged if your points are met its requirements.</string>
    <string name="reward_details">Reward Details</string>
    <string name="c_points_needed">C-Points needed</string>
    <string name="points">points</string>
    <string name="details">Details</string>
    <string name="coming_soon">Coming Soon</string>
    <string name="change_profile">Change Profile</string>
    <string name="faq">FAQ</string>
    <string name="send_feedback">Send Feedback</string>
    <string name="logout">Logout</string>
    <string name="app_version">App Version 1.0</string>
    <string name="save">Save</string>
    <string name="what_is_cycleme">What is CycleMe?</string>
    <string name="cycleme_description">CycleMe is a mobile application that enables users to classify waste based on pictures they capture. The app requires camera access and an active internet connection. With CycleMe, you can share your recycling journey through the Feed feature, where you can post images and videos accompanied by captions. Other than that, you can interact with other users by leaving comments on their posts. If you have recycled products to sell, our Marketplace feature has you covered. Please ensure that you follow any guidelines or restrictions provided by the app for content upload in the Feed feature and adhere to specific policies related to selling products in the Marketplace. We hope you enjoy using CycleMe!</string>
    <string name="how_to_use_description">The waste classification feature in CycleMe enables users to capture a picture of waste, and the application will then display the type of waste along with recycling recommendations. To utilize this feature, follow these steps:\n\n1. Grant Camera Access:\n\u2022 Allow your device to access the camera by adjusting the necessary permissions in the device settings.\n\n2. Capture Waste Image:\n\u2022 Tap the camera icon within the app.\n\u2022 Position the garbage in the frame using your device\'s camera. Ensure good lighting conditions when capturing waste images\n\u2022 Capture the image by pressing the shutter button.\n\n3. View Waste Classification:\n\u2022 The app will classify the waste and display the classification label. It may require some time for processing\n\u2022 Additionally, it will provide recommendations for recycled products related to the waste category.\n\n4. Explore Recycled Product Options:\n\u2022 If you are interested in creating a specific product, tap on one of the recommended recycled products.</string>
    <string name="title">Title</string>
    <string name="feedback_title">Feedback Title</string>
    <string name="feedback">Feedback</string>
    <string name="write_feedback">Write Feedback</string>
    <string name="send">Send</string>
    <string name="notification">Notification</string>
    <string name="you_don_t_have_notification_yet">You don\'t have notification yet</string>
    <string name="textiles">Textiles</string>
    <string name="plastic">Plastic</string>
    <string name="upload_feed">Upload Feed</string>
    <string name="let_s_share_your_work">Let\'s share your work</string>
    <string name="description">Description</string>
    <string name="you_can_explore_the_popular_recycling_categories">You can explore the popular recycling categories</string>
    <string name="share_the_excitement_to_your_friends">Share the excitement to your friends</string>
    <string name="share_caption2">Let’s make the world a better place\nBy Sharing CycleMe app to your friends :)</string>
    <string name="share_cycleme">Share CycleMe</string>
    <string name="share_cycleme_description">CycleMe is a mobile application that empowers users to classify waste based on pictures they capture or upload. Once a photo is uploaded, the app will identify the waste type and provide recommendations on recycled products tutorials. With CycleMe, users can share their recycling journey through the Feed feature, where they can post image accompanied by captions. By uploading an image to the Feed, users will earn points that can be redeemed for exciting rewards. We highly value user feedback as it contributes to the ongoing improvement of our application. We hope you enjoy your experience with CycleMe!\n\nYou can download CycleMe through this link: https://ipb.link/cycle-me-app</string>


    <!-- Article Items -->
    <string-array name="titles">
        <item>Why Is Recycling Important? 10 Benefits of Recycling</item>
        <item>How Does Recycling Help the Environment?</item>
        <item>Common Recycling Myths</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="descriptions">
        <item>Why is Recycling Important?\n\n
            1. Protects Ecosystems and Wildlife\n
            When we recycle, we lessen disruption to the natural world. When we cut down fewer trees and forests, we are preventing harm to animals. By reducing disruption and damage to the natural world, we help preserve ecosystems and wildlife.\n\n
            2. Conserves Our Natural Resources\nSome of the world’s natural resources are in short supply, and when we recycle, we help conserve these natural resources. When we recycle paper, we save forests and trees. When we recycle plastic, it takes up a lot of solid waste and can take centuries to break down. In addition to this, most plastic comes from fossil fuel hydrocarbons. Recycling metals reduces the need to extract new metal ore while recycling glass reduces our need for certain raw materials like sand.\n\n
            3. Saves Energy\nMaking products from recycled materials requires less energy than making them from new, raw materials. It takes much less energy to make products out of recycled materials than from raw materials. For example, recycling one glass bottle saves enough power to light a 100-watt light bulb for four hours.\n\n
            4. Reduces the Need to Harvest New Materials\nWhen we recycle, it reduces our need to harvest raw materials. Our increasing demand for these raw materials also displaces people who live near forests or around river systems. When we recycle, we reduce the possibility of damaging someone else’s land or community.\n\n
            5. Reduces Carbon Emissions\nRecycling takes up less energy, which reduces our carbon footprint and emissions. Reducing our carbon footprint helps minimize methane-release waste from landfill sites, which contributes to climate change.\n\nSource: https://northhillbottledepot.ca/why-is-recycling-important-10-benefits-of-recycling/</item>

        <item>Here are a few ways recycling helps the environment and fight climate change:\n\n
            1. Recycling Conserves Resources\nWhen we recycle plastic, we reduce the need for more plastic to be manufactured. By recycling paper, we do our part to lessen deforestation and save trees from being cut down. Separating cans and other metals helps to cut down on damaging mining and our growing need for raw materials.\n\n
            2. Recycling Saves Energy\nIt takes much more energy to create industrial-grade materials from scratch than it does just to reform old materials and reuse them. For example, it is estimated that “recycling aluminum saves 90% to 95% of the energy needed to make aluminum from bauxite ore.” Recycling saves energy because recycled materials don’t require factories to expend so much greenhouse gas emissions than they would if they had created the same item again from scratch using raw materials.\n\n
            3. Recycling Protects the Environment\nWhen we cut down on the amount of new materials and natural resources we need to extract from the earth, whether through farming, mining, logging, etc., we protect vulnerable ecosystems and wildlife from harm or eradication and allow them to exist for generations to come. Recycling materials emits way less greenhouse gases into the environment than primary production.\n\nSource: https://www.goodwall.io/blog/how-does-recycling-help-the-environment/</item>
        <item>Learn the reality behind the myths to ensure you\'re protecting others and the environment by recycling right.\n\n
            Myth: Recycling arrows on a container mean it is definitely recyclable\n
            Reality: Only in some cases. Check the table above and local program guidelines to see what\'s recyclable and what\'s not. Many plastics cannot be made into new products. Recycle plastics by shape: bottles, jars, jugs and tubs.\n\n

            Myth: Containers must be squeaky clean in order to be recycled\n
            Reality: Containers should be clean, but don\'t have to be spotless. While all bottles, cans and containers should be clean, dry and free of most food waste before you place them in your recycling container, they don’t need to be spotless. The goal is to make sure they are clean enough to avoid contaminating other materials, like paper, or your un-lined kitchen recycling bin. Try using a spatula to scrape cans and jars, and putting recyclables in your sink among the dishes you are rinsing to share that same water to rinse and remove residue.\n\n

            Myth: Even if an item shouldn\'t go in the bin, it will get sorted anyway\n
            Reality: False. Non-recyclable items are not accepted curbside. Non-recyclable items contaminate recyclables. Recyclables stuck inside plastic bags are at risk for never making it through the recycling process. Conversely, recyclable items placed into garbage containers are hauled to a landfill and cannot be recovered effectively. The right thing to do is put the right recyclables in the recycling container and non-recyclables into garbage containers. Recyclables with the greatest impact are bottles, cans, paper and cardboard.\n\nSource: https://www.wm.com/us/en/recycle-right/recycling-101</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="images">
        <item>@drawable/article_1</item>
        <item>@drawable/article_2</item>
        <item>@drawable/article_3</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Recycle Items -->
    <string-array name="recycle_label">
        <item>Upload Photo</item>
        <item>Aluminium</item>
        <item>Carton</item>
        <item>Glass</item>
        <item>Organic Waste</item>
        <item>Paper and Cardboard</item>
        <item>Plastic</item>
        <item>Styrofoam</item>
        <item>Textiles</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recycle_desc">
        <item>Recycle your waste</item>
        <item>8 ideas</item>
        <item>6 ideas</item>
        <item>10 ideas</item>
        <item>4 ideas</item>
        <item>20 ideas</item>
        <item>12 ideas</item>
        <item>4 ideas</item>
        <item>8 ideas</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="recycle_image">
        <item>@drawable/waste_photo</item>
        <item>@drawable/waste_aluminium</item>
        <item>@drawable/waste_carton</item>
        <item>@drawable/waste_glass</item>
        <item>@drawable/waste_organic_waste</item>
        <item>@drawable/waste_paper_and_cardboard</item>
        <item>@drawable/waste_plastic</item>
        <item>@drawable/waste_styrofoam</item>
        <item>@drawable/waste_textiles</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Reward Items-->
    <string-array name="reward_title">
        <item>Electricity Token Rp20.000</item>
        <item>Voucher Cashback Gopay Rp5.000</item>
        <item>Plant Real Trees in Kalimantan</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="reward_point">
        <item>200</item>
        <item>400</item>
        <item>700</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="reward_image">
        <item>@drawable/reward_logo_pln</item>
        <item>@drawable/reward_logo_gopay</item>
        <item>@drawable/reward_logo_plant</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="reward_banner">
        <item>@drawable/reward_banner_pln</item>
        <item>@drawable/reward_banner_gopay</item>
        <item>@drawable/reward_banner_plant</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="reward_detail">
        <item>\u2022 Your accumulated points will be redeemed with Rp20.000 electricity token (token listrik PLN).\n\u2022 You can enter the 20 digit electricity token (electric token number) into the electric meter.\n\u2022 Terms and conditions apply.</item>
        <item>\u2022 Your accumulated points will be redeemed with Rp5.000 cashback voucher.\n\u2022 The voucher can be used when shopping using Gopay.\n\u2022 Terms and conditions apply.</item>
        <item>\u2022 You contribute a small sum of Rp10.000 for each redemption.\n\u2022 We purchase high-quality carbon credits and contribute to tree-planting projects in Indonesia.\n\u2022 The carbon credits from the project contribute to the protection and restoration of forests at risk of deforestation in Central Kalimantan, Indonesia.\n\u2022 This prevents the release of greenhouse gas emissions from deforestation activities.\n\u2022 They work with tree-planting partners to plant trees across Indonesia. This promotes the absorption of greenhouse gases from the atmosphere.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>